https://www.robichauxlaw.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Robichaux Law Firm, LLCPrivacy Policy - Robichaux Law Firm, LLC
Call Now To Receive A Free Legal Evaluation (504) 332-8188HomeAbout UsOur TeamJ. Van Robichaux, Jr.Renée M. Robichaux, Esq.Michael A. Gorbaty, Esq.Karen Robichaux (Office Manager)Valerie Heintz (Legal Assistant)Wanda Alcon (Legal Assistant)Firm OverviewPractice AreasAsbestos & MesotheliomaAutomobile AccidentsAviationBicycle AccidentsBirth TraumaBrain InjuriesClass ActionsDefective DrugsDefective ProductsInsurance ClaimsLyft & Uber AccidentsMaritime InjuriesMass TortsMedical MalpracticeMotorcycle AccidentsNursing Home NegligenceSlip & Fall AccidentsSpinal Cord InjuriesToxic Tort LitigationWills & Successions18-Wheeler & Semi-Truck
AccidentsTestimonialsZantac CasesBlogsVideosContact UsMenu HomeAbout UsOur TeamJ. Van Robichaux, Jr.Renée M. Robichaux, Esq.Michael A. Gorbaty, Esq.Karen Robichaux (Office Manager)Valerie Heintz (Legal Assistant)Wanda Alcon (Legal Assistant)Firm OverviewPractice AreasAsbestos & MesotheliomaAutomobile AccidentsAviationBicycle AccidentsBirth TraumaBrain InjuriesClass ActionsDefective DrugsDefective ProductsInsurance ClaimsLyft & Uber AccidentsMaritime InjuriesMass TortsMedical MalpracticeMotorcycle AccidentsNursing Home NegligenceSlip & Fall AccidentsSpinal Cord InjuriesToxic Tort LitigationWills & Successions18-Wheeler & Semi-Truck
AccidentsTestimonialsZantac CasesBlogsVideosContact Us Privacy PolicyYour privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. Get Help NowHome » Privacy PolicyHomeTerms Of UsePrivacy PolicyContact UsLawyer MarketingDisclaimer: Material presented on the Robichaux Law Firm, LLC
website is intended for information purposes only. It is not intended as professional advice and should not be construed as such. Any unauthorized use of material contained herein is at the user’s own risk. Transmission of the information and material herein is not intended to create, and receipt does not constitute, an agreement to create an attorney-client relationship with the Robichaux Law Firm, LLC or any member thereof. This website is not intended to be advertising and the Robichaux Law Firm, LLC does not wish to represent anyone desiring representation based upon viewing this website in any state or jurisdiction where this website fails to comply with all laws and ethical rules. Some links within this website may lead to other sites. Robichaux Law Firm, LLC does not necessarily sponsor, endorse or otherwise approve of the materials appearing in such sites.Copyright©2020, Robichaux Law Firm, LLC. All Rights Reserved.
